A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Joseph E. Persico, Series 12 FA381
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Pre-Vice Presidential Speeches, 1966-1974; 3; 6.4 Cubic Feet
  - Center for Inter-American Relations Dinner, New York City, May 14, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 426)
  - International House Banquet, New York City, May 15, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 427)
  - Remarks of NAR at the New York State Council on the Arts Luncheon, Buffalo, New York, May 16, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 428)
  - Harlem State Office Building Dedication, New York City, May 20, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 429)
  - Remarks of NAR at the 10th Annual Republican Legislative Dinner, Lansing, Michigan, May 22, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 430)
  - Bar Association of Nassau County Award Dinner, Hypogaea, New York, May 23, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 431)
  - National Republican Heritage Groups Council, New York City (Cancelled), May 24, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 432)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Association for A Better New York, New York City, May 31, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 433)
  - Remarks of NAR at the 42nd Convention Edison Electric Institute, New York City, June 5, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 434)
  - Taft School Commencement, Watertown, Connecticut, June 9, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 435)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union Convention, Miami, Florida, June 11, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 436)
  - Remarks of NAR at the Republican State Convention, Uniondale, New York, June 12, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 437)
  - Remarks of NAR at the New York Republican State Dinner, New York City, June 13, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 438)
  - Cuyahoga-Lake Republican Fund-Raising Dinner, Cleveland, Ohio, June 14, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 439)
  - Wyoming Republican State Committee Dinner, Cheyenne, Wyoming, June 18, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 440)
  - Republican Fund-Raising Barbecue Dinner, Tulalip Indian Reservation, Everett, Washington, June 19, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 441)
  - Republican Fund-Raising Luncheon, Spokane, Washington, June 19, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 442)
  - International Convention National Newspaper Association and the Canadian Community Newspaper Association, Toronto, Canada, July 26, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 443)
  - Maine Republican Committee Dinner, Bangor, Maine, August 9, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 444)
  - Republican Governors Conference, Chicago, Illinois, August 11, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 445)
  - Remarks of NAR as Prepared for Delivery at the White House, August 20, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 446)
  - Fund-Raising Dinner for Jim Nugent for Governor, Newport, Rhode Island, August 21, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 447)
  - Press Conferences I and II (Location Unknown), August 23, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 448)
  - Press Questions of NAR, Washington, D. C., August 28, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 449)
  - Press Questions of NAR on Arrival at Westchester Airport, White Plains, New York, August 31, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 450)
  - News Conference of NAR, New York City, September 3, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 451)
  - Bank of Tokyo Opening, New York City, September 6, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 452)
  - Sidewalk Conference of NAR, September 9, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 453)
  - Remarks of NAR Before Religious Zionists of America, New York City, September 12, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 454)
  - Joint Meeting of the Republican National Committee and Finance Committee, Washington, D. C., September 16, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 455)
  - United Nations Ambassadors Dinner, New York City (Cancelled), September 18, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 456)
  - Governors Club Outing, Pocantico, New York, September 20, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 457)
  - Interview with NAR, October 10, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 458)
  - Interview with NAR, October 11, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 459)
  - Press Interview with NAR, October 15, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 460)
  - Press Conference with NAR, October 16, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 461)
  - Confirmation Hearings Press Conference, New York City, October 21, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 462)
  - NAR Monthly Speech Index, 1966-1970 (Box 22, Folder 463)
  - NAR Monthly Speech Index, 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 464)
- Press Releases, 1970-1974; 4; 1.2 Cubic Feet
  This is a collection of press releases, which includes transcripts of interviews, press conferences, and speeches.
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign Releases, June-July 1970 (Box 23, Folder 465)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign Releases, August 1970 (Box 23, Folder 466)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign Releases, September 1970 (Box 23, Folder 467)
  - 1970 Gubernatorial Campaign Releases, October 1970 (Box 23, Folder 468)
  - NAR Program Papers (Aging - Federalism), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 469)
  - NAR Program Papers (Health - Youth), 1970 (Box 23, Folder 470)
  - Press Releases, January-February 1970 (Box 23, Folder 471)
  - Press Releases, March-April 1970 (Box 23, Folder 472)
  - Press Releases, May 1970 (Box 23, Folder 473)
  - Press Releases, June 1970 (Box 23, Folder 474)
  - Press Releases, July 1970 (Box 24, Folder 475)
  - Press Releases, August 1970 (Box 24, Folder 476)
  - Press Releases, September 1970 (Box 24, Folder 477)
  - Press Releases, October 1970 (Box 24, Folder 478)
  - Press Releases, November-December 1970 (Box 24, Folder 479)
  - Press Releases, January-February 1971 (Box 24, Folder 480)
  - Press Releases, March-April 1971 (Box 24, Folder 481)
  - Press Releases, June-July 1971 (Box 24, Folder 482)
  - Press Releases, July-August 1971 (Box 24, Folder 483)
  - Press Releases, September-October 1971 (Box 24, Folder 484)
  - Press Releases, November-December 1971 (Box 24, Folder 485)
  - Press Releases, January-February 1972 (Box 25, Folder 486)
  - Press Releases, March-April 1972 (Box 25, Folder 487)
  - Press Releases, May-June 1972 (Box 25, Folder 488)
  - Press Releases, July-August 1972 (Box 25, Folder 489)
  - Press Releases, September-October 1972 (Box 25, Folder 490)
  - Press Releases, November-December 1972 (Box 25, Folder 491)
  - Press Releases, January-February 1973 (Box 25, Folder 492)
  - Press Releases, March-April 1973 (Box 25, Folder 493)
  - Press Releases, May-June 1973 (Box 25, Folder 494)
  - Press Releases, August-September 1973 (Box 25, Folder 495)
  - Press Releases, October-November 1973 (Box 25, Folder 496)
  - Press Releases, December 1973 (Box 25, Folder 497)
  - Press Releases, January-February 1974 (Box 25, Folder 498)
  - Press Releases, March-April 1974 (Box 25, Folder 499)
  - Press Releases, May-June 1974 (Box 25, Folder 500)
  - Press Releases, July-August 1974 (Box 25, Folder 501)
  - Press Releases, September-October 1974 (Box 25, Folder 502)
  - Press Release Index, 1966-1968 (Box 25, Folder 503)
- Miscellaneous Files, 1958-1974; 5; 1.2 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains Nelson Rockefeller's quotations on major issues, an article for the American Academy of Political and Social Science on revenue sharing, program papers on topics such as aging and the economy, and subject indices for speeches.
  - Article - Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science - Revenue Sharing, April 20, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 504)
  - Article - Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science - Revenue Sharing, April 20, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 505)
  - Program Papers (Aging - Crime Control), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 506)
  - Program Papers (Economy - Labor), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 507)
  - Program Papers (Mental Disability - Youth), 1973 (Box 26, Folder 508)
  - Nelson Rockefeller Quotations on Major Issues, April 1974 (Box 27, Folder 509)
    Excerpts from speeches and statements by NAR as Governor, as Chair of the Commission on Critical Choices for Americans, and as the National Commissioner on Water Quality.
  - Subject Index of Speeches - Alphabetical, 1959-1971
    - Abortion - Buses, 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 510)
    - Campaign - Culture, 1958-1971 (Box 27, Folder 511)
    - Defense Contracts - Extremism, 1958-1971 (Box 27, Folder 512)
    - Farm Economy - Gun Control, 1958-1971 (Box 27, Folder 513)
    - Harness Racing Commission - Juvenile Delinquency, 1958-1971 (Box 27, Folder 514)
    - Kassel, Mortimer - Luce, Claire Booth, 1959-1971 (Box 27, Folder 515)
    - Major Medical - Nuclear Testing, 1958-1971 (Box 27, Folder 516)
    - Obituaries - Puerto Rico, 1958-1971 (Box 28, Folder 517)
    - Racing - Symbol, State, 1958-1971 (Box 28, Folder 518)
    - Taconic Parkway - Truman, Harry S., 1958-1971 (Box 28, Folder 519)
    - Un-American Activities Committee - Youth, 1958-1971 (Box 28, Folder 520)